var question = [
    {
      question: "Who did 007 fight in a traincar in From Russia with Love?",
      choices: ["Le Chiffre", "Jason Bourne", "Red Grant", "Jaws"],
      answer: "Red Grant",
    },
    {
      question: "Who directed Skyfall?",
      choices: ["Steven Spielberg", "Michael G. Wilson", "Kathryn Bigelow", "Sam Mendes"],
      answer: "Sam Mendes",
    },
    {
      question: "Who sang the theme song 'Goldeneye'?",
      choices: ["Tina Turner", "Shirley Bassey", "Sam Smith", "Tom Jones"],
      answer: "Tina Turner",
    },
    {
      question: "How many official James Bond movies are there?",
      choices: ["22", "23", "24", "25"],
      answer: "25",
    },
    {
      question: "How many official James Bond actors have there been?",
      choices: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
      answer: "6",
    },
    {
      question: "What is 007's quartermaster known as?",
      choices: ["M", "Miss Moneypenny", "Q", "Greg from State Farm"],
      answer: "Q",
    },
    {
      question: "Regarding the Chief of MI6 played by Dame Judy Dence, what does the codename 'M' stand for?",
      choices: ["Marcus", "Miss Moneypemnny", "Emma", "Noone Actually Knows"],
      answer: "Noone Actually Knows",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the standard issue sidearm assigned to the 00 agenst?",
      choices: ["Desert Eagle", "Colt 45", "Walther PPK", "Luger"],
      answer: "Walther PPK",
    },
    {
      question: "What was Pierce Brosnan's first film as James Bond?",
      choices: ["Goldeneye", "Goldfinger", "Goldmember", "Property of a Lady"],
      answer: "Goldeneye",
    },
    {
      question: "Complete the name of this James Bond film: 'You Only Live _____",
      choices: ["Once", "Twice", "Three Times a Lady", "Forever"],
      answer: "Twice",
    },
    {
      question: "What card game do the gamblers in Casino Royale play?",
      choices: ["Texas Hold 'Em", "Baccarat", "Five Card Draw", "Seven Card Stud"],
      answer: "Texas Hold 'Em",
    },
    {
      question: "What group does 007's ally, Felix Leiter, work for?",
      choices: ["The NSA", "The CIA", "Scotland Yard", "OSS"],
      answer: "The CIA",
    },
    {
      question: "What luxury sports car does MI6 usually furnish 007 with?",
      choices: ["Aston Martin", "Jaguar", "Alfa Romeo", "Citroen"],
      answer: "Aston Martin",
    }
  ];